NARRATOR: Previously on
AMC's "The Walking Dead"...
RICK: We're gonna have
Daryl leading them away.
20 miles more.
I'll take a car
and ride next to him.
It can't just be him.
You doing this
cuz you wanna die?
No.
We don't need to go
looking for people anymore.
Feel different about it?
Yeah. I do.
- (HORN HONKS)
- DARYL: (ON RADIO) What's going on back there?
RICK: (ON RADIO)
Half of them broke off!
They're going toward Alexandria!
You keep going!
What is it?
Keep moving. I'll catch up.
Hee ya!
Abraham!
I'm just livin' darlin'.
Woo!
Just like you.
(SNARLING)
SASHA: (ON WALKIE) All right.
DARYL: (ON WALKIE) That's 20?
SASHA: It will be.
642 is a mile ahead.
We gotta put distance between
us and them before the turnoff.
ABRAHAM: (ON WALKIE) So floor it.
DARYL: All right.
try to keep up.
SASHA: Daryl. have you
looked at this car?
(CHUCKLES) Believe me. we
want to get back there. too.
(GUNFIRE)
(GUNFIRE CONTINUES)
(BULLETS RICOCHETTING)
(ENGINE STARTS)
(TYRES SQUEALS)
(GUNFIRE)
(GRUNTS)
(GUNFIRE CONTINUES)
(SNARLING)
Leave it.
Just gonna give it
a last little polish.
What the hell
you got to grin about?
We won. darlin'.
There could be more.
- (TYRES SQUEALING)
- (CARS APPROACHING)
Screw it.
(PANTING)
(WALKER GROWLING)
(THEME MUSIC PLAYING)
Improved By: Fidel33
Sub Upload Date: November 17. 2015
(BIRDS CALLING)
(GRUNTING)
(PANTING)
Sasha?
Abraham. are you there?
(STATIC HISSING)
(WINCING)
(EXHALES)
(BRANCH SNAPS)
(RUSTLING)
You found us. okay?
Here we are.
We earned what we took.
(BRANCH SNAPS)
(THUMPS)
(ECHOING) Probably just another
soldier from one of the outposts.
Probably hates him. too.
(ECHOING)
You know how to use one?
(MAN'S VOICE ECHOING) Yeah.
Never liked using them to hunt.
(ECHOING) We pick up Patty
and we're gone. okay?
This is the last day
we gotta live like this.
(CRICKETS CHIRPING)
Get up.
Hey. get up.
(GUN CLICKS)
We're moving.
Here's the deal.
You don't say shit
and I don't kill you.
I ain't who you think.
- (HAMMER CLICKS)
- Say something else.
Go ahead.
Follow them.
Here. drink the rest.
- We should save it.
- We'll find some more.
Drink.
You're supposed
to stay hydrated.
It all works together.
Yeah. it does.
Have it.
We don't need you falling down.
Drink.
They find us. maybe
we give you to them.
they let us call it even.
You see.
we're reasonable people.
Everybody's got their code.
You feel you gotta kneel.
that's fair enough.
We don't.
Let's go.
I can't believe we're back.
It's not home anymore.
but it's better
than where we were.
This is a pit stop.
We pick up Patty.
nothing more than that.
How'd you do it?
You saw where we left the truck?
Mm-hmm.
We opened the valve and drove all
the way in from Farmview Road.
Ran from the tree line
till we got to the pavement.
Lit up a matchbook
from the Sweetwater
- and dropped it in on the trail.
- (GROWLING)
Then we just ran for the car.
Got in and the dead
ones were there.
They were beating
on the hood. and then--
and then boom!
Knocked 'em on their asses
and I took an axe to each one.
Then we just watched it go up.
No more moans. no
more of that wailing.
It was just the fire.
just burning them all away.
You did all this?
It was right at the start.
Everything stopped--
the TV. the radio.
We were here.
The forest was full of them.
And the other ones in town.
they were drawn to it.
They just walked
right into the flames.
We got most of them.
Thought we ended it for us.
and she was in DC.
We thought everyone was fighting
them wherever they were.
Yeah. we thought that was
what everybody was doing.
Fighting it.
That we'd all win together.
We were stupid.
Y'all don't think you're
being stupid right now?
(HAMMER CLICKS)
Are you saying
I should kill you?
I mean it. are you gonna try
and pull something on us?
Are we just being thick here
by not removing all doubt?
Right now. by me
not pulling this trigger.
is that a mistake?
I'm serious.
I really wanna know.
You made a choice
to kill for someone else.
to have them own you for a roof
over your head and three squares.
so maybe I'm not considering
all aspects here.
You tell me. am I being stupid?
No.
Look. I got somewhere to be.
We can make a deal.
I can help you out.
You're one of them.
You're hurt and you're alone
and you'd say anything.
We should've never trusted
you people to begin with.
Go on.
Keep moving.
(WALKERS GROWLING)
Son of a bitch.
(GROWLING CONTINUES)
Patty.
She could be...
(WOMAN SIGHS)
No. she's gone.
Then we make another plan.
Yeah. we get out of here.
that's the plan.
Then that's the plan.
You guys didn't have
to do this for me.
It was the right
thing for all of us.
This was the right thing?
Even if just you guys
went back now.
if you just told them
that it was me...
No. we'll find a way.
- Just think about it.
- No.
Look. maybe we don't get as
far. but we'll get-- hey!
- Hey. hey. hey!
- Tina. hey!
Hey. baby sister. look at me.
Hey. stop!
No!
(GUNSHOTS)
Don't!
We need that. please!
(PANTING)
Sasha. Abraham. are you there?
(STATIC HISSING)
(WALKER GROWLING)
(GROWLING)
(SNARLING)
(SNARLING CONTINUES)
(PANTING)
SASHA: There. it's clear.
His bike's gone.
These are his shells.
He fired at 'em. got away.
He caught a good bounce.
There aren't
enough people around
to just wait around
for somebody to ambush.
And they couldn't have
just been watching us.
not with what we were doing.
Nah. they were looking to chew
up someone in particular.
Whoever the hell they were.
Daryl. you copy?
(STATIC HISSING)
Daryl?
Dollars to doughnuts. he's on
his way back to Alexandria now.
- He wouldn't leave us behind.
- He already did.
But he came back.
So we go look for him.
The best way to find a
tracker is to stay put.
Let him find you.
You just want us to sit here
with our precious leathers
in our hands?
No.
(WALKER GROWLING)
Don't.
What?
You're smarter than that.
We don't need
to leave bread crumbs.
(DOOR CREAKS)
(DOOR CLOSES)
(FLASHLIGHT CLICKS)
(SNARLING)
How come gorgeous over here
is still standing?
He can't get out.
(THUMPING)
It's locked.
We're fine.
Stand watch or sleep?
Your choice.
I'll take the former.
Do a little shopping. maybe.
(THUMPING CONTINUES)
(GROWLING)
(DRAWERS RATTLING)
(WALKER SNARLS)
(GROWLING)
(BAG THUDS)
Can't sleep?
What does it look like?
I just wanted to know
if it was a choice.
(WALKER GROWLING)
(SIGHS)
You have no idea how much
I want to release that thing
from this plane of existence.
(WALKER GROWLING)
(SIGHS. CHUCKLES)
This our new home?
Should we give him a name?
You got yourself into this.
I was driving that car solo
until you chose to come with.
Oh. I didn't have
a choice there.
Tell me why.
You going stag
was not an option.
Tell me why.
You were out of control
for a good while there.
Just about took my arm off
on the road to paradise.
- You remember that?
- I do.
- I'm in control now.
- Me. too.
That's why you wanna
kill that walker?
The one down the street?
The guys in the car?
'Cause you're in control.
'Cause loose ends
make my ass itch.
If I have not gotten
my psyche situated straight.
it's because the shit's
continually been hitting the fan
without respite.
Oh. there's been respite.
There was a party.
Oh. I remember that.
You had the time
of your life there.
You don't have to throw
yourself out of a moving car...
to feel like
you're calling the ball.
That's easy.
You jump out of an airplane.
you don't have
choices after that.
Maybe you play some
chicken with the ground.
but you pull the rip
cord. you live.
But if you have
a roof over your head.
you have food. you have walls...
you have choices.
And without walkers and bullets
and shit hitting the fan.
you're accountable for them.
I mean. hell. you're
always accountable.
It's just with
all that other noise.
you know people won't notice.
(GROWLING)
Stand watch or sleep.
The former.
Straight through the night.
We'll reassess in the morning.
What do you mean?
What the hell we're doing here.
Drop the gun.
Drop it.
Give it to me.
I came all this way.
What you got for the duffel?
You put me through too much
shit just to give it back.
Principle of the thing.
What you got besides this gun?
Nothing.
What was that thing
you were carving?
- My grandfather taught me how--
- DarylMDARYL: Don't care.
It'll do.
Take it.
It's all there.
Good luck.
You're gonna need it.
(TREES SNAPPING)
(BRAKES SQUEALING)
(TRUCK DOOR OPENS. CLOSES)
Let's end this.
It's ours.
We earned what we took.
MAN: You're gonna
return what you took.
You're gonna pay for the gas
it took to come out here
and for all the time
these men took out.
It's over.
You know the rules.
Your rules are batshit!
We're not going back. Wade.
We're done kneeling!
Don't change the subject.
asshole.
- (WHISTLES)
- (TRUCK ENGINE REVS)
(TREES SNAPPING)
(BRAKES SQUEALS)
Come on.
Hey. that way.
Go. go. go.
Go.
Get up.
(TREES SNAPPING)
Hey.
Take it.
- (WALKIE STATIC HISSES)
- WADE: (ON WALKIE) Eyes open.
You cover your quadrant.
Go to alpha channel.
(GROWLING)
(WEAKLY) Love you. Sher.
You didn't have to for me.
(MUMBLING)
(RUSTLES)
- (SNARLING)
- (SCREAMING)
Wade. I'm bit!
- Take it off me.
- Damn it.
Do it!
Just take it off!
WADE: I'll get your watch after.
(MAN SCREAMS. CRYING)
- (WALKIE STATIC HISSES)
- WADE: All right. that's it.
Time to go home.
Cam got a boo-boo.
MAN: (ON RADIO) Are you sure?
WADE: Oh. yeah. He only
wanted to take this so far.
And he only wants ass
that's willing. you know?
(SOBBING)
Come on. Cam.
Let's walk it off.
We thought you were with them.
We knock you over the
head. tie you up.
threaten to kill you...
why the hell did you come back?
(GRUNTS)
Maybe I'm stupid. too.
(BIRDS CHIRPING)
(GUN CLICKING)
(GROWLING)
Well. howdy. gentlemen.
(GROWLING CONTINUES)
(METAL CREAKING)
(CLATTERING)
RPG.
(METAL CREAKING)
(ROARING)
(CHUCKLES)
(MATCH STRIKES)
- (SNARLING)
- (FLESH SQUELCHING)
(METAL GROANING)
(SPLATS)
(WALKER SNARLING. THUDS)
SASHA: Where do you get that?
It is the fruit
of some off-the-chart
stupidity.
Some grade-A.
butt steak idiocy.
Self-awareness
is a beautiful thing.
Yes. it is.
You see. I know this group
and I know Rick.
And whatever happened
back there is being managed
and kicked right up
into its own ass
one way or another.
I know that.
We got beer...
and air conditioning...
and walls.
The table is set
for the rest of our lives.
and I hope those years
to be long and fruitful.
I see that time before me...
and I've been feeling the
urge to make some plays...
before the great cosmic Pete comes
to cut my throat unceremoniously
and I gurgle my last breath.
Well. things are gonna go on
for a while before that.
and that hadn't
occurred to me before.
I've been kind of living
check to check on that point.
I like the way
you call bullshit. Sasha.
I believe I'd like to get to
know you a whole lot better.
(CHUCKLES)
That one of your plays?
What makes you think
I want that?
A man can tell.
(LAUGHS)
Well...
(CHUCKLES) ...you got
some stuff to take care of.
Yeah.
I do.
DARYL: So you knew 'em?
Still you thought I was one of them?
Where we were-- we were
there since the beginning.
We still didn't know everyone.
Back when we first
threw in with them.
it was as good
as a place as any.
Then things got harder.
people got harder.
Human nature kicked in
and it became
a truly unique kind of shitshow.
People will trade
anything for safety.
for knowing that they're safe.
Everything.
So they got nothing left
except just...
existing.
Hey. nobody's safe anymore.
Can't promise
people that anyhow.
You could promise the
people who want to hear it.
Hey. Tina. hold up.
Carla and Delly.
That's them.
HONEY: Me and Tina used to babysit
them when they were kids.
Everyone said that they went
out north when it all started.
We didn't know.
(RUSTLING)
I did this.
We did this.
- (GROWLING)
- (SCREAMING)
- (SOBBING)
- I'm sorry!
- (COUGHS)
I'm so sorry. baby.
We had to try.
We had to.
(HONEY SOBBING)
I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry.
I'm...
Hey.
How many walkers you killed?
- Just answer the question.
- A lot.
A couple dozen at least.
How many people you killed?
None.
Why?
Why haven't I killed anybody?
Because if I did.
there'd be no going back.
There'd be no going back
to how things were.
I'm from a place
where people are
still like they were...
more or less. better or worse.
I can walk it from here.
Till we meet up with my friends.
(GRUNTS)
They got a car.
You can ride with them.
How many friends
you say there were?
I didn't.
There's two of 'em.
Where are they?
We're gonna find out.
How do you know they even got away?
That they didn't get taken?
I don't.
- (HAMMER CLICKS)
- Oh. damn it.
I'm sorry.
Give her the crossbow.
You gonna go back?
- You gonna be safe?
- Shut up.
Ain't nowhere safe no more.
Give her the crossbow.
You gonna kneel?
(GUNSHOT)
(ENGINE STARTS)
Patch yourself up.
We're sorry.
You're gonna be.
(GROWLING SOFTLY)
(GROWLING)
(GROWLING STOPS)
- (WALKER GROWLING)
- Look at this.
What?
Nothing.
(TRUCK APPROACHES)
(TRUCK ENGINE STOPS)
(CHUCKLES)
Rick. you copy?
(STATIC HISSING)
DARYL: Anybody?
(STAIC HISSING)
(GARBLED VOICE OVER RADIO)
DARYL: Say it again?
(STATIC HISSING)
MAN: (ON WALKIE) Help.
Improved By: Fidel33
Sub Upload Date: November 17. 2015
(THEME MUSIC PLAYING)